lindstromtools.com 2017-06-25

# Lindström precision tools

The privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy are for this site only. Other SNA Europe affiliate Web sites may have different practices. If you link to or otherwise visit these or any other Web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

The privacy of your personally identifiable information is important to us. As part of our commitment to the privacy of your personally identifiable information, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information is requested.

The privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy are for this site only. Other SNA Europe affiliate Web sites may have different practices. If you link to or otherwise visit these or any other Web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**The Information We Collect**

SNA Europe will comply with national data protection laws that govern the collection and use of personal information, such as the Swedish Data Protection Act (Personuppgiftslagen 1998:204), and which will apply to the activities of SNA Europe. Under the Swedish Personal Data Act you have rights of access and rectification in relation to your personal information. SNA Europe will adhere to such rights as far as possible to fulfill SNA Europe's legal obligations.  
In general, when you visit our site you remain anonymous, but on some pages, you need to provide personally identifiable information to register and contact SNA Europe. The types of personally identifiable information collected at these pages may include Name, Company, Customer Number (if applicable), Address, E-mail, Address, Phone Number, Fax Number.

We might also enable you to submit information about other people. For example, we might request that you provide us with information about your distributor or dealer's name and contact information.

**The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide to communicate with you, for example, to answer the e-mail and correspondence we receive. We may use your information to make recommendations for products or special offers, and to provide you with updates on new products that we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive this information in the future, please contact us here.

From time to time, we may share certain information with select third parties including distributors or dealers in your area to enable them to process orders, fulfill your requests or to offer products or services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to share your information, please contact us here.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request.

We will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Customization and Aggregate data**

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and gather information for product management and development at SNA Europe. For example, we may tell our sales and marketing staff that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our Web site during a particular time period, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. This aggregate information may also be shared with distributors or dealers.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Cookies**

When you view one of our web sites, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" and will help us better serve you. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Any information gathered by the use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis. Cookies cannot contain virus or harmful program code. It does not require large space on your hard drive and can be deleted.

This information allows us to measure site activity and to tailor information to suit your individual preferences, for example subscription of news. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful visit. By showing how and when our visitors use this web site, this information can help us to improve our web site on a continual basis.  

If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so. In Netscape you find these settings in Edit / Preferences / Privacy & Security (Advanced in older versions) and in Internet Explorer in Tools / Internet Options / Security (Privacy or Advanced in older versions).

**Children's Privacy**

SNA Europe has no intention of collecting personal information from children at this site.

**Changes to the Policy**

Our privacy practices, like the online medium itself, are subject to change. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement at our site.

**How to Contact Us**

SNA Europe is the controller of the personal data processed through your use of the site. You are entitled to, upon request, receive notification from us whether we process any of your personal data and, if such data is processed, which information about you that is processed; where this information has been collected; the purpose of the processing; and to which recipients or categories of recipients the information is disclosed. Such notification on your request may be given free of charge once per year.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies or wish to have your personally identifiable information deleted from our records, please send an email to [info@bahco.com](mailto:info@bahco.com) or mail correspondence to SNA Europe, BP 20104 Eragny, 956 13 Cergy Pontoise, France.
